Rahul Mishra

rahulmishra102000@gmail.com / 9829104911 / https://rahul-mishra.netlify.app, Jaipur, Rajasthan

Summary

Innovative and proactive cyber security researcher capable of developing elegant security policies, and scanning for the vulnerabilities in the nwtwork and website. Talented in project management, team leadership and independent problem-solving. Highly organisied multitasking with experties in scheduling projects, enhancing designs and verifying security policies. Prepared to offer penetration testing, shell scripting and python scripting abilities to challenging role.

Experience

Python Developer Intern

Conscript 04/2020 - 06/2020

This was a project based python development internship. The project of our team was named as Question Assessment Tool, the main feature of this system is to evaluate the answers provided by the students/test takers. I helped in designing the database of this project, helped in developing the algorithm to evaluate the Multiple Choice Questions and Subjective Answers, and front-end of the website.

Subject Matter Expert

Intellify

04/2020 - 06/2020

In this internship I was working as a Subject Matter Expert (Python), in this internship we have to make an explanation related to any programming problem in the form of power point presentation, and then we have to make an explanatory video on the very same problem.

Education

B.Tech CSE

University of Engineering and Management • Jaipur, Rajasthan

• Currently completing bachelors degree in computer science, batch 2018-2022

Class 12

Kendriya Vidyalaya No. 2 • Jaipur, Rajasthan 05/2018

• I did my 10+2 from Kendriya Vidyalaya No. 2, and secured 74% in boards examinations.

Skills

- Penetration Testing
- · Shell Scripting
- MySQL
- Linux

- Python
- Burp Suite
- Git

- · Web Development
- C++
- GitHub